Guide to the Merton Stoltz Files 1959-1978
Brown University Library
- Files: 1965-1966, 1960-1967; Series 3
  - Academic Departments, Series 3. Subseries C
    - Solid Mechanics Group, 1965 (Box 18, Folder III.92)
    - Art, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder III.93)
    - Biological and Medical Sciences, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder III.94)
    - Paul F. Fenton, Chairman, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder III.95)
    - Biology -- Herman B. Chase, 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder III.96)
    - Medicine -- Mac V. Edds, Jr., 1965-1966 (Box 18, Folder III.97)
    - Medical Education, 1966 (Box 19, Folder III.98)
    - Chemistry, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.99)
    - Classics, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.100)
    - Computing Lab, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.101)
    - Economics, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.102)
    - Center for Fluid Dynamics, 1966 (Box 19, Folder III.103)
    - Education, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.104)
    - Egyptology, 1965 (Box 19, Folder III.105)
    - Engineering, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.106)
    - English, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.107)
    - French, 1965 (Box 19, Folder III.108)
    - Geology, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.109)
    - German, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.110)
    - History, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.111)
    - Linguistics, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.112)
    - Mathematics, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.113)
    - Philosophy, 1965 (Box 19, Folder III.114)
    - Physics, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.115)
    - High-Energy Physics, 1965 (Box 19, Folder III.116)
    - Political Science, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.117)
    - Political Leadership, 1965 (Box 19, Folder III.118)
    - Psychology, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.119)
    - Religious Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.120)
    - Slavic Languages, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.121)
    - Sociology and Anthropology, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder III.122)
- Files: 1966-1967, 1965-1968; Series 4
  - Committees, Series 4. Subseries A
    - Computer Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.1)
    - Committee on Environmental Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.2)
    - Research and Investigation Involving Human Beings -- Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.3)
    - Committee on Large Systems Design and Management, 1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.4)
    - Magrath Committee, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.5)
    - Profile, 1964 (Box 20, Folder IV.6)
    - Applied Math/Math/Geological Sciences Building, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.7)
    - Biomedical Complex, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.8)
    - Building for the Departments of Earth Sciences/Pure Mathematics/Applied Mathematics, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.9)
    - Graduate Center, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.10)
    - Humanities Building, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.11)
    - Office Building, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.12)
    - Pembroke Dormitory, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.13)
    - Physical Sciences Library, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder IV.14)
    - Committee on Summer Interns, 1966 (Box 20, Folder IV.15)
  - General, Series 4. Subseries B
    - Admissions, 1966 (Box 21, Folder IV.16)
    - Cambridge Radio Observatory Committee (CAMROC), 1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.17)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.18)
    - Chaplain, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.19)
    - F. Morris Cochran, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.20)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.21)
    - Howard Curtis, Secretary, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.22)
    - Asian Studies, 1966 (Box 21, Folder IV.23)
    - East Asia Language and Area Center, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.24)
    - East European Program, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.25)
    - EDUCOM, 1966 (Box 21, Folder IV.26)
    - Foreign Student Office, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.27)
    - General Faculty Research Reserve, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.28)
    - Graduate School -- General, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.29)
    - Health Sciences Advancement Award -- Proposal, 1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.30)
    - Themis, 1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.31)
    - Institute for Health Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.32)
    - Child Development Study, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.33)
    - Mental Retardation Center, 1967 (Box 21, Folder IV.34)
    - International Relations, 1966 (Box 21, Folder IV.35)
    - Peace Corps, 1966 (Box 21, Folder IV.36)
    - M.S. Stevens, 1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.37)
    - Office of Summer and Special Programs, 1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.38)
    - Tougaloo, 1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.39)
    - Tougaloo, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.40)
    - University Chairs, 1965-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.41)
    - Universities Research Association, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.42)
    - WBRU, 1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.43)
    - Personal, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.44)
  - Academics Departments, Series 4. Subseries C
    - Art, 1965 (Box 22, Folder IV.45)
    - Biomedical Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.46)
    - Medical Education, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.47)
    - Medicine -- M.V. Edds, Jr., 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.48)
    - Radiation Therapy Center, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.49)
    - R.I. Hospital and Brown Joint Facilities, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder IV.50)
    - High Pressure Physiology, 1996 (Box 23, Folder IV.51)
    - Classics, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.52)
    - Computing Laboratory, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.53)
    - Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.54)
    - Education, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.55)
    - Engineering, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.56)
    - Center for Fluid Dynamics, 1966 (Box 23, Folder IV.57)
    - English, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.58)
    - Haffenreffer Museum, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.59)
    - Linguistics, 1966 (Box 23, Folder IV.60)
    - Music, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.61)
    - Philosophy, 1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.62)
    - Physics, 1966 (Box 23, Folder IV.63)
    - Political Science, 1966 (Box 23, Folder IV.64)
    - Psychology, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.65)
    - Sociology and Anthropology, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder IV.66)
    - Board of Review for Academic Freedom, 1968 (Box 23, Folder IV.67)
- Files: 1967-1968, 1964-1968; Series 5
  - Committees, Series 5. Subseries A
    - Animal Care and Utilization Committee, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.1)
    - ARPA Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.2)
    - ARPA Program -- Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.3)
    - Committee to study Benefits for Faculty and Appointed Members, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.4)
    - Center for Biophysical Sciences and Biomedical Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.5)
    - Program Committee in Biomedical Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.6)
    - Program Committee in Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.7)
    - Program Committee in Theoretical and Mathematical Biophysics, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.8)
    - Center for Computer and Information Sciences, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.9)
    - Human Subjects Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.10)
    - Committee on Large Systems Design and Management, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.11)
    - Applied Math/Math/Geological Sciences Building, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.12)
    - Graduate Center, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.13)
    - Sciences Library, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.14)
    - Space Sciences Committee, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.15)
    - Study Committee for Student Union Facilities, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.16)
  - General, Series 5. Subseries B
    - Vivian B. Allen Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.17)
    - David E. Clark -- Administrative Intern, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.18)
    - F. Morris Cochran, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.19)
    - Excellence Program, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.20)
    - Ford Foundation, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.21)
    - Ray L. Heffner, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.22)
    - "K" Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.23)
    - Child Study Center, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.24)
    - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.25)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1968 (Box 24, Folder V.26)
    - NASA, 1966 (Box 24, Folder V.27)
    - NSF -- Center for Information Sciences, 1967 (Box 24, Folder V.28)
    - NSF -- Institutional, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.29)
    - NSF -- Senior Foreign Scientist Program, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder V.30)
    - New England Radio Observatory Corporation (NEROC), 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.31)
    - Providence College, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.32)
    - Registrar -- M. Noble, 1968 (Box 25, Folder V.33)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder V.34)
    - Raymond G. Studer, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.35)
    - Themis, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.36)
    - Tougaloo, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.37)
    - Universities Research Association, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.38)
    - University Chairs, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.39)
    - WBRU, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.40)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution, 1965-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.41)
  - Academic Departments, Series 5. Subseries C
    - Art, 1968 (Box 25, Folder V.42)
    - Biological and Medical Sciences, 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.43)
    - Dr. Henry M.S. Uhl -- Office of Continuing Medical Education, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.44)
    - Committee on Radiation Therapy Center, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder V.45)
    - P.F. Fenton, Chairman, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.46)
    - Dr. Pierre M. Galletti -- Chairman of Division, 1968 (Box 26, Folder V.47)
    - Biology -- E.H. Leduc, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.48)
    - Classics, 1968 (Box 26, Folder V.49)
    - Engineering, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.50)
    - English, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.51)
    - Geological Sciences, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.52)
    - Military Science, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.53)
    - Haffenreffer Museum, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder V.54)
- Files: 1968-1969, 1967-1969; Series 6
  - Committees, Series 6. Subseries A
    - Committee for European-American Center, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.1)
    - Human Subjects Committee, 1968 (Box 27, Folder VI.2)
    - Physical Sciences Council, 1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.3)
    - Haffenreffer Project, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.4)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.5)
  - General, Series 6. Subseries B
    - African Studies, Black Literature, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.6)
    - Vivian B. Allen Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.7)
    - The Louis Calder Foundation, 1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.8)
    - East Asia Language and Area Center, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.9)
    - Five Year Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.10)
    - Ford Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.11)
    - Paul F. Maeder -- Associate Provost, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.12)
    - NSF Institutional, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.13)
    - NSF Development Program -- Engineering, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.14)
    - NSF -- Applied Mathematics, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.15)
    - NSF -- Chemistry, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.16)
    - Department of Geological Sciences, [undated] (Box 27, Folder VI.17)
    - NSF -- Mathematics, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder VI.18)
    - NSF -- Physics, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.19)
    - NSF -- Proposal for Research and Training Activities, 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder VI.20)
    - NSF -- Federal Research, Training and Facilities Support, 1967 (Box 28, Folder VI.21)
    - Personnel and Degrees Awarded by Department, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.22)
    - NSF -- Federal Research, Training and Facilities Support, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.23)
    - NSF -- Student Data, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder VI.24)
    - Pembroke College, 1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.25)
    - Richard King Mellon Charitable Trusts, 1967 (Box 28, Folder VI.26)
    - New England Radio Observatory Committee (NEROC), 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.27)
    - John Price, 1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.28)
    - Public Relations Planning Group, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.29)
    - "R" Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.30)
    - Registrar -- M. Noble, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.31)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1968 (Box 28, Folder VI.32)
    - Ten-Year Projected Program, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.33)
    - Tougaloo College, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.34)
    - Transition Year Program, 1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.35)
    - Personal, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.35A)
    - Affiliation Agreement, 1969 (Box 28, Folder VI.36)
    - Annual Report -- Office of Continuing Medical Education, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.37)
    - Continuing Education in Medicine -- Dr. Uhl, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.38)
    - General Matters, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.39)
    - Hospital Relations, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.40)
    - Liaison Committee on Medical Education (AMA), 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.41)
    - Lying-In Hospital, 1968 (Box 29, Folder VI.42)
    - Roger Williams Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.43)
    - University-Affiliated Mental Retardation Center, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.44)
    - Radiation Therapy Center, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.45)
    - State Department of Health, 1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.46)
  - Academic Departments, Series 6. Subseries C
    - Art, 1969 (Box 29, Folder VI.47)
    - Computing Laboratories, 1968 (Box 29, Folder VI.48)
    - Center for Fluid Dynamics, 1968 (Box 29, Folder VI.49)
    - Proposed Graduate Programs -- History of Religions, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder VI.50)
- Files: 1969-1970, Series 7
  - Committees, Series 7. Subseries A
    - Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.1)
    - Campus Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.2)
    - Committee on Community Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.3)
    - Committee on Creative and Performing Arts, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.4)
    - Committee on Curricular Philosophy -- Special Educational Principles, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.5)
    - ROTC Policy, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.6)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Housing and University Expansion, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.7)
    - Study Committee on Pembroke College, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.8)
    - University Council on Student Affairs, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.9)
    - Planning Committee for Community Health Laboratory, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.10)
    - R.I. Health Services Research, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.11)
    - Council on Library Resources (Project INTREX-MIT), 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder VII.12)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.13)
    - Equal Opportunity, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.14)
    - Acting President File, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.15)
    - Mr. Stoltz, 1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.16)
    - Military Recruiting, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.17)
    - Student Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.18)
    - Enrollment and Admissions Data, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.19)
    - Brown University Press, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.20)
    - Art Center, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.21)
    - Bond Bread Site, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.22)
    - Bryant College, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.23)
    - Haffenreffer Project, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.24)
    - Dean of the College, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.25)
    - Dean of Pembroke College, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder VII.26)
    - East European Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.27)
    - University Excellence Project, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.28)
    - Ford Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.29)
    - NSF Survey -- Scientific Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.30)
    - NSF Development, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.31)
    - NERComP (New England Regional Computing Program), 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.32)
    - Pembroke College, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.33)
    - Tougaloo College, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.34)
    - Transitional Year College, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.35)
    - American Civilization, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.36)
    - Division of Biological and Medical Sciences, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.37)
    - Joint University-Hospital Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.38)
    - R.I. Group Health Association, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.39)
    - Rhode Island Hospital, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.40)
    - Roger Williams General Hospital, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.41)
    - Radiation Therapy Center, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.42)
    - Classics, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.43)
    - Computing Laboratories, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder VII.44)
    - East Asian History, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.45)
    - Education, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.46)
    - French, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.47)
    - History, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.48)
    - Libraries -- D. Jonah, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.49)
    - Linguistics, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.50)
    - Music, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.51)
    - Physics, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.52)
    - Political Science, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.53)
    - Policy Science Center, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.54)
    - Slavic Languages, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.55)
    - Sociology and Anthropology, 1969-1970 (Box 33, Folder VII.56)
- File: 1970-1971, Series 8
  - Committees, Series 8. Subseries A
    - Center for Bio-physical Sciences and Biomedical Engineering, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.1)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.2)
    - Tax Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.3)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.4)
    - American Council on Education, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.5)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.6)
    - Council on Library Resources (Project INTREX/MIT), 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.7)
    - Rhode Island Health Services Research, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.8)
    - Brown/Pembroke Consolidation, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.9)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.10)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.11)
    - Dean of the Graduate School, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.12)
    - Development Office, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.13)
    - East European Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.14)
    - European-American Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.15)
    - Extension Division, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder VIII.16)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.17)
    - NSF Center for Information Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.18)
    - NSF Institutional Development, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.19)
    - NSF Social Sciences Development, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.20)
    - NSF NATO Postdoctoral Fellowships in Science, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.21)
    - Graduate Center, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.22)
    - Eric Brown, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.23)
    - Kenan, William R., Jr. Charitable Trust, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.24)
    - Maeder, Paul F., 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.25)
    - Planning, Programming, Budgeting in the Private University, [undated] (Box 35, Folder VIII.26)
    - New England Radio Observatory Committee (NEROC), 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.27)
    - Performance Study, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.28)
    - Price, John, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.29)
    - Copy Center Program -- F. Lees, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.30)
    - Alfred E. Sloan Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.31)
    - Tougaloo College, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder VIII.32)
  - Academic Departments, Series 8. Subseries B
    - Anthropology (Box 35, Folder VIII.33)
      Missing as of 2020 February 4
    - Afro-American Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.34)
    - Afro-American Society, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.35)
    - American Civilization, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.36)
    - Applied Mathematics, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.37)
    - Biological and Medical Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.38)
    - Medical Program Analysis, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.39)
    - Hospital Relations, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.40)
    - Classics, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.41)
    - Egyptology, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.42)
    - Engineering, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.44)
    - Geological Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.45)
    - Library Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.46)
    - Policy Sciences Planning Group, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.47)
    - Religious Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.48)
    - Sociology, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder VIII.49)
- Files: 1971-1972, Series 9
  - Committees, Series 9. Subseries A
    - Campus Planning Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.1)
    - Library -- Faculty Advisory Committee (CLR-NEH), 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.2)
    - Planning and Building Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.3)
    - Renaissance and Medieval Study Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.4)
    - Committee on Urban Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.5)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.6)
    - Committee on Appointment of Women Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.7)
    - Brown Alumni Monthly (BAM), 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.8)
    - Chaplain's Office, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.9)
    - Civil Rights Act, 1964, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.10)
    - East European Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.11)
    - Initial Overview of Management Information Systems for Brown University, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.12)
    - HEW Science Project, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.13)
    - Miscellaneous Matters, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.14)
    - NSF Senior Foreign Scientist Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.15)
    - Grants and Contracts, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.16)
    - Kenan, William R., Jr. Charitable Trust, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.17)
    - Office of Analysis and Plans, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.18)
    - McLaughry, John (Summer Programs), 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.19)
    - Placement Office, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.20)
    - Wage and Price Freeze, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder IX.21)
    - Provost's Office, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.22)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.23)
    - Sloan Study Policy Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.24)
    - Stevens, Malcolm S., 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.25)
    - Brown University Working Papers on Housing, 1971 (Box 38, Folder IX.26)
    - Untermeyer Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.27)
    - WBRU, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.28)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.29)
  - Academic Departments, Series 9. Subseries B
    - Afro-American Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.30)
    - American Civilization, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.31)
    - Anthropology, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.32)
    - Art, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.33)
    - Biological and Medical Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.34)
    - M.D. Program, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder IX.35)
    - Medical Program Analysis, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.36)
    - Hospital Relations, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.37)
    - Committee on Medical Ethics, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.38)
    - Chemistry, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.39)
    - Classics, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.40)
    - Computing Laboratory, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.41)
    - Education, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.42)
    - Egyptology, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.43)
    - Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.44)
    - English, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.45)
    - French, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.46)
    - German, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.47)
    - Libraries, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.48)
    - Library Study Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.49)
    - Military Sciences, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.50)
    - Music, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.51)
    - Music Ad Hoc Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder IX.52)